xi3.com 2012-12-05

# Xi3 | Privacy Policy

Xi3's privacy policy covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by The Xi3 Corporation™ anytime you interact with Xi3, such as when you visit our website or when you call our inquiry department. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Xi3, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

**Why we collect personal information**  
Why do we collect your personal information? Because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest announcements, updates and events that you might like to hear about.

**What information we collect**  
There are certain situations in which your personal information may help us give you better service. We may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites and Internet services are of most interest to them.

**When we disclose your information**  
Xi3 takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that Xi3 does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the Xi3 group globally who will safeguard it in accordance with Xi3’s privacy policy. There are also times when it may be advantageous for Xi3 to make certain personal information about you available to companies that Xi3 has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Xi3 to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with Xi3’s policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the Xi3 website.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

**How we protect your personal information**  
Xi3 takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

**Cookies and other technologies**  
As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Xi3’s website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. ISYS will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

**Privacy questions**  
If you have questions or concerns about the Xi3 Privacy Policy or data processing, please use our contact form Labeling it Xi3 Privacy Policy Question in the description.

© 2010 Xi3 Corporation. All rights reserved.
